<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cv xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="/home/meggleton/Projects/cv/cv-schema2.xsd">
  <candidate>
    <name>Martyn Eggleton</name>
    <address>
      <line>118 Fairbarn Drive</line>
      <line>Stannington</line>
      <city>Sheffield</city>
      <postcode>S6 5QL</postcode>
    </address>
    <mobile>07583 445696</mobile>
    <email>martyn.eggleton@gmail.com</email>
    <twitter>stretchyboy</twitter>
    <linkedin>martyn-eggleton-9348a8a</linkedin>
    <github>stretchyboy</github>
    <dateofbirth>27th July 1976</dateofbirth>
    <nationality>British</nationality>
    <maritalstatus>Divorced</maritalstatus>
  </candidate>
  <profile>
    <item>
      <category>training</category>
      <category>mentoring</category>
      <description>Excellent training and mentoring skills for software developers, teaching good practices and agile techniques etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <category>community</category>
      <description>A keen free and open source software developer who contributes to and leads various small FLOSS projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>music</category>
      <category>programming</category>
      <description>An Algorave enthusiast, I perform with FoxDot at local gigs and on global live streams, improvising EDM using FoxDot and Python code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <category>programming</category>
      <description>A skilled programmer with over 15 years experience in web technologies especially  HTML, Python, JavaScript, PHP and Node.js.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <description>Dedicated to bringing the most efficient and usable user experience to new and existing systems, by bring forward innovative, creative ideas and developing them into complete systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>communication</category>
      <description>A hardworking individual with experience of working in small teams as well as written, verbal and visual communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <description>Flexible, adaptable and self developing with an aptitude for picking up ICT systems and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>design</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>training</category>
      <description>An aptitude for software development, systems design, education and training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>software</category>
      <description>Good awareness of design, planning &amp; problem solving techniques and approaches in a variety of situations from developing functional specifications    for technical solutions with users, to process development, training, team and capacity building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>development</category>
      <category>web development</category>
      <description>Good web development skills both aesthetically and technically, with a strong commitment to clean code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
          <category>ICT</category>
      <description>Flexible, adaptable and self developing with an aptitude for picking up ICT systems and techniques 			 (I am currently learning JAVA for 3D games development and XUL for an Internet aware song lyric and presentation projection suite).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>programming</category>
      <description>Flexible, adaptable and self developing with an aptitude for picking up programming languages, ICT systems and techniques 			 (I am currently learning A-Frame for web based VR development).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>software</category>
      <category>development</category>
      <description>Experience of high profile and high financial turnover environments, writing for systems with an annual turnover in excess of 14 million pounds			and being the mostly responsible for the 'Flora London Marathon Exhibition' website.</description>
    </item>
<item>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Good training and mentoring skills ranging from identifying learners needs to preparing sessions and giving feedback and assessment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>-
      <description>Good classroom and workshop teaching skills and exposure to teacher training at <a href="http://shu.sc.uk">SHU</a> (Withdrew due to accidental injury).</description>
      </item>
<item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>learning</category>
      <description>Good classroom and workshop teaching skills and exposure to teacher training (CertEd) at <a href="http://shu.sc.uk">Sheffield Hallam University</a> unfortunately I could not complete due to accidental injury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>A hardworking individual with good interpersonal, written, verbal and visual communications skills and an aptitude for software development, coaching, learning materials and training.</description>
    </item>

  </profile>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation href="http://utcsheffield.org.uk/">Sheffield University Technical College</organisation>
    <date year="2013" month="09"></date>
    <title>Skills Trainer, Creative Digital Media &amp;  Computing</title>
    <summary>
    </summary>
    <item>
      <category>vr</category>
      <category>System Design</category>
      <description>Part of co-design process for a new PlayStation VR, Educational Environmental Narrative game as part of the
        <a href="http://revealvr.eu">REVEAL</a> project with
        <a href="http://www.steelminions.com/">The Steel Minions</a> and <a href="https://www.shu.ac.uk/">
      Sheffield Hallam University</a> and EU partners through
      <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/programmses/horizon2020/">Horizon2020</a>.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>programming</category>
      <category>languages</category>
      <category>c++</category>
      <category>c#</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Leading A' Level Computing project process for 20+ students from ideation &amp; planning to mentoring coding  &amp;
      debugging in C++, C#, Python, JavaScript &amp; PHP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>programming</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Teaching requirements capture, design thinking, design diagramming, agile, UML and extreme programming techniques, OOP etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>security</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Teaching cyber security theory and techniques to students for the CyberEPQ qualification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <description>Lead teaching GCSE Computing to various groups, including planning the Schemes of Work, tracking data and student / parent feedback. The course includes both the theory of computer science and the practicalities of programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>evaluation</category>
      <description>Analysing and evaluating the progress of students and the learning techniques used to improve progress and attainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>git</category>
      <category>mentoring</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <category>tdd</category>
      <category>C#</category>
      <category>C++</category>
      <description>Teaching version control (git), team working technologies (gitlab, github, issue tracking etc.) and test driven development, using JavaScript, C#, C++ and Python languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>python</category>
        <description>Developing web based solutions to various issues for school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>documentation</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>computing</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>programming</category>
      <description>Implementing interactive blended learning materials (HTML, JavaScript etc.) and documentation of techniques and software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>computing</category>
      <description>Delivering innovative physical learning aids, including the <a href="https://github.com/EduMake/walking-cpu">walking-cpu</a> software which produces poster and worksheets for students to explore and discover "Fetch Decode Execute".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>mentoring</category>
      <description>Project mentoring of student-led projects, using a wide range of technologies. Recent projects include dancing drones, importing LIDAR data into MineCraft and web based mapping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <category>computing</category>
      <category>python</category>
      <description>Heavily using Raspberry Pi for teaching of theory, physical computing and engineering. Using and contributing to the PiNet community and building tools like logicexplorer, a physical logic gate / circuit simulator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Supporting the teaching of Creative Digital Media skills, assisting with photography, graphic design, audio and video editing.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation href="https://www.mozillafestival.org/en/">Mozilla</organisation>
    <date year="2012" month="10"></date>
    <date year="2017" month="11"></date>
    <title>MozFest - Youth Zone Facilitator</title>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Delivering technical workshops and children's activities at <a href="https://mozillafestival.org/">MozFest</a>.</description>
    </item>
    <!--<item>
    <category>Leadership</category>
    <description>Hoping to be on the next Mozilla Open Leadership Training course. </description>
    </item>-->
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation href="http://access-space.org">Access-Space</organisation>
    <date year="2015" month="08"></date>
    <date year="2019" month="11"></date>
    <title>Trustee</title>
    <summary>
    </summary>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation>EduMake</organisation>
    <date year="2012" month="05"></date>
    <date year="2019" month="09"></date>
    <title>Learning Technologist</title>
    <summary>Founder member of the Digital Makers Educational Co-operative. Taking on small projects and developing learning materials.</summary>
    <item>
      <category>project lead</category>
      <category>self led</category>
      <description>Main developer and project lead on our Education and Development projects ensuring milestones are met.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Developing micro accreditation scheme using <a href="https://openbadges.org/">Open Badges</a> and approaches combining Blooms Taxonomy and the Experience API.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>emerging technology</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <description>Building Amazon Alexa Skills and learning materials for students to make their own voice activated software for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>less</category>
      <category>handlebars</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <description>Designed the software for <a href="http://junctionarts.org/data-draw/">Data-Draw</a>, a machine for capturing survey data in a tactile and engaging way. It then produces engaging generative animated art works, unique to each visitor from the data. The individual receives a paper version and can see themselves or the whole day of visitors on-line. The system is written in JavaScript using HTML, SVG, LESS and Handlebars templating, producing a very adaptable system for use by many organisations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>vr</category>
      <category>emerging technology</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <description>Experimenting with Virtual Reality learning materials starting with <a href="https://vr-atoms.herokuapp.com/">vr-atoms</a>, GCSE Chemistry atom models built in WebVR / A-frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Built "<a href="https://active-learn.herokuapp.com/">active_learn</a>" and "active_JavaScript" adaptive learning environments, which give differentiated learning paths way for			GCSE Computing maths skills and JavaScript programming skills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Using the Waterbear project to build graphical programming interfaces for teaching physical computing to children as young as 5.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation href="http://access-space.org">Access-Space</organisation>
    <date year="2009" month="01"></date>
    <date year="2013" month="04"></date>
    <title>Technical Manager</title>
    <summary>
    </summary>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>css</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>education</category>
      <description>Designed and taught workshops on many different technical subjects from installing software to developing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and designing Robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>linux</category>
      <description>Built a hardware auditing linux distro with hardware testing, recording and printing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <description>Taught customers how to build PCs to fit their needs from recycled parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>community</category>
      <description>Worked within a community setting and led the volunteer hardware team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>css</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Built various WordPress / DokuWiki and Moodle plugins in PHP, that generate HTML &amp; CSS for educational purposes and council run projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>css</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Developed light touch peer learning tracking software for monitoring and reporting of the progress of informal learning networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>floss</category>
      <description>Shared knowledge of FLOSS (Free/Libre Open Source Software), philosophy utilities and tools (and the ethos behind them) for development with other users including creativity programs,			editors and programming libraries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>css</category>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <description>Created various Access-Space Web pages including modifying HTML templates for dokuwiki.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation href="http://access-space.org">Access-Space</organisation>
    <date year="2008" month="07"></date>
    <date year="2008" month="12"></date>
    <title>Training / Technical Volunteer</title>
    <summary>
    </summary>
    <item>
      <category>linux</category>
      <description>Taught workshops with Access-Space users introducing Linux and FLOSS (Free/Libre Open Source Software) and how to install and configure a GNU/Linux distribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <description>Taught users how to refurbish second user IT equipment and how to select build and test PCs from component parts.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation>CMJ Management Ltd.</organisation>
    <date year="2003" month="05"></date>
    <date year="2008" month="06"></date>
    <title>Software Developer</title>
    <summary>Software Developer on TAMS (Total Agency Management System) which provides back office and white label public websites for booking accommodation and conference facilities and equipment and exhibition space.</summary>
    <item>
      <category>system design</category>
      <description>Worked closely with internal and external customers identifying, proposing and implementing new features to improve user experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>full-stack</category>
      <category>lamp</category>
      <category>orm</category>
      <description>Full-stack development in a multiserver LAMP environment. Developing our in house ORM and presentation components</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <category>databases</category>
      <description>Relational Database design and maintenance using PostgreSQL on a system comprising of well over 100 tables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Developed major 'Hotel Booking Agency Management System' written in object oriented PHP			with an in house frame work that I helped to develop, this included extensions to SMARTY.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Wrote and was responsible for design, maintenance and user support for a user definable report writing module, which output as HTML/CSS, CSV and PDF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Wrote Web 2.0 style JavaScript rendered user interface elements for quick searches and situations where there are many small incremental updates to be made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>system design</category>
      <category>project lead</category>
      <description>Project lead on our work for the 'London Marathon Exhibition', developing T-Shirt printing, exhibition design, sales and promotional web sites.</description>
    </item>
        <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>svg</category>
      <description>Wrote a cross browser rich Internet application for designing lettering for t-shirts and running vests for the Flora London Marathon, in object oriented JavaScript using JSON as the communication medium, and CSS styling.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>svg</category>
      <category>hardware</category>
      <category>hpgl</category>
      <description>Built web based T-shirt manufacture system including material minimsing batch management and a SVG plotter driver in PHP for HPGL2 based cutter plotters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>svg</category>
      <category>xml</category>
      <description>Wrote graphical exhibition floor-plan designer in SVG and JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>javascript</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>svg</category>
      <description>Wrote a user edited content management system that, allowed Exhibitors at the Flora London Marathon to add there own content and logos to the lmexpo website safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>xml</category>
      <description>Wrote XML / REST interfaces for connection to partner organisations systems, for single sign-in etc.	And integration with Google Checkout and WorldPay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <category>tdd</category>
      <description>Designed and coded using TDD in internally built library, ensuring further robustness.</description>
    </item>
    <departure>CMJ was wound up after the emigration of our owner.</departure>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation>jobnet @ burtonstreetproject</organisation>
    <date year="2002" month="09"></date>
    <date year="2003" month="04"></date>
    <title>Advice Worker / IT Coordinator</title>
    <summary>Advised job seekers and developed software that matched their skills to local jobs &amp; training.</summary>
    <item>
      <category>advising</category>
      <description>Advised and assisted people on job search issues and help them to develop and find work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>system design</category>
      <description>Advised on the development of the externally developed Skills Register' system to fix it functionality and usability issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Developed tools to assist colleagues in other jobnets (15 offices around Sheffield) and JobCentrePlus offices to classify jobs in to the Standard Occupational Classification Codes, the first version being in CHM the second MS Access 2000 and the final one written in PHP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>php</category>
      <description>Developed distributed systems to allow our advise workers to write CVs for clients, track the kind of work they are looking for and do semi automated job search on a number of websites, from any location. Again initially in ACCESS (as front end to PostgreSQL) but then in PHP.</description>
    </item>
    <departure>I was starting to consider a move into full time software development and was invited to join CMJ by the project lead.</departure>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation>Jobcentre Plus</organisation>
    <date year="2000" month="06"></date>
    <date year="2002" month="09"></date>
    <title>Administration Officer</title>
    <summary>Assistant Disability Employment Adviser, Occupational Psychology Assessment Test Administrator,			Access to Work Administration Assistant &amp; Assistant Access to Work Consultant.</summary>
    <item>
      <category>advising</category>
      <description>Assisted disabled jobseekers to find work by advising on employment and benefit issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>advising</category>
      <description>Administered Occupational Psychology Assessment exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>system design</category>
      <description>Assisted the team to administer the programme. Due to Employment Services IT policy I had to develop a complex management information and reporting system in EXCEL, to replace the DiSC system. I was also asked to develop the Functional Specification for permanent the replacement DiSC2.</description>
    </item>
    <departure>I left JCP to help start JobNet as I still had links with the community organisations involved and had the skills and knowledge.</departure>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation href="http://www.wildsheffield.com/">Sheffield Wildlife Trust</organisation>
    <date year="1998" month="11"></date>
    <date year="2001" month="03"></date>
    <title>Information and Publicity Manager</title>
    <summary>Managed all the internal information systems, developed 6 database systems, some of which loaded live data into the website I built using PERL, and others that were used for financial tracking, and reserve management.</summary>
    <item>
      <category>databases</category>
      <category>web</category>
      <category>html</category>
      <category>perl</category>
      <description>Managed all the internal information systems, developed 6 database systems, some of which loaded live data into our website using PERL, and others that were used for financial tracking, and reserve management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>design skills</category>
      <description>Responsible for producing SWT's publications including the membership magazine Kingfisher and brochures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <category>system admin</category>
      <description>Administered a PC network, installed software, coached staff, advised SWT and others on purchasing, and provided all user support.</description>
    </item>
    <departure>This was a originally a 1 year contract, but was extended whilst funding allowed.</departure>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid">
    <organisation>Crossfield Chemicals</organisation>
    <date year="1993" month="07"></date>
    <date year="1993" month="09"></date>
    <title>Thixotropic paint systems researcher</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Work Experience">
    <organisation>Garog</organisation>
    <date year="1993" month="03"></date>
    <date year="1993" month="03"></date>
    <title>Digital systems design assistant</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Work Experience">
    <organisation>Heronscan Software Ltd</organisation>
    <date year="1992" month="02"></date>
    <date year="1992" month="02"></date>
    <title>Digital control systems design assistant</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation>Neighbourhood Information Network Enterprise</organisation>
    <date year="1998" month="02"></date>
    <date year="1998" month="09"></date>
    <title>Technical Manager</title>
    <item>
      <description>Co-founder and developer for project aiming to use information technology to help socially excluded communities help themselves, through information, knowledge and resource sharing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>This involved putting together a draft Neighbourhood Atlas, a 250 page website.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation href="http://www.zestcommunity.co.uk/">Netherthorpe and Upperthorpe Community Alliance</organisation>
    <date year="1997" month="10"></date>
    <date year="1998" month="09"></date>
    <title>Management Committee Member</title>
    <item>
      <description>Founder member, officer and executive member for organisation that brings together over 70 community groups in the area to give local people a say in how regeneration funding is spent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Also a member of the committee responsible for the use of European funding, and involved in writing the Area Action Plan and the organisation of the community conference and consultation on which it was based.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation>The Word Place</organisation>
    <date year="1997" month="04"></date>
    <date year="1997" month="12"></date>
    <title>IT Tutor to ESOL students</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation>Gimme5</organisation>
    <date year="1996" month="05"></date>
    <date year="1996" month="12"></date>
    <title>Project team member</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation>Students For Sheffield</organisation>
    <date year="1996" month="01"></date>
    <date year="1996" month="09"></date>
    <title>Committee Member</title>
    <item>
      <description>Heavily involved in this partnership between students, community and business leaders in Sheffield to improve the effectiveness of students in the community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>I completed the first Leadership in the Community' course in 96, and helped stage courses in 97 and 8. Led the Audio and Visual team that staged 3 highly successful conferences for 1200 people.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary">
    <organisation>Sheffield Electronic Press</organisation>
    <date year="1995" month="09"></date>
    <date year="1996" month="05"></date>
    <title>Project Leader</title>
    <item>
      <description>First Editor &amp; technical manager for the worlds first student run independent student internet newspaper, ShEP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Responsible for introducing it's continuing organisational structure and initial launch, and setting up and managing many of its technical elements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Organised and motivated volunteer reporters, programmers and editorial staff.</description>
    </item>
  </experience>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>AMT International</organisation>
    <date year="1999" month="08"></date>
    <date year="1999" month="08"></date>
    <qualification type="City &amp; Guilds" level="3" title="7331 in Training Techniques"></qualification>
  </educationitem>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>University of Sheffield</organisation>
    <date year="1994" month="10"></date>
    <date year="1996" month="06"></date>
    <qualification type="BEng" title="Control &amp; Systems Engineering" grade="200 CAT Points" level="4"></qualification>
  </educationitem>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>Padgate High 6th Form Centre</organisation>
    <date year="1992" month="09"></date>
    <date year="1994" month="06"></date>
    <qualification type="A Level" level="3"  title="Maths" grade="A"></qualification>
    <qualification type="A Level" level="3"  title="Physics" grade="B"></qualification>
    <qualification type="A Level" level="3"  title="Economics" grade="C"></qualification>
    <qualification type="A Level" level="3"  title="General Studies" grade="A"></qualification>
  </educationitem>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>Padgate County High School</organisation>
    <date year="1987" month="09"></date>
    <date year="1992" month="06"></date>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="Maths" grade="A"></qualification>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="Dual Award Science" grade="AA"></qualification>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="English Lit &amp; Lang" grade="BB"></qualification>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="Music" grade="F"></qualification>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="British Industrial Society" grade="B"></qualification>
    <qualification type="GCSE" level="2"  title="German" grade="C"></qualification>
  </educationitem>
  <referee name="Ifatgar Ahmed" title="Curriculum Director for Computing">
    <organisation>UTC Sheffield - Olympic Legacy Park</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>UTC Olympic Legacy Park</line>
      <city>Sheffield</city>
      <postcode>S9 3TU</postcode>
    </address>
    <tel>0114 260 3940</tel>
    <email>iahmed@utcsheffield.org.uk</email>
  </referee>
  <!--	
    <referee name="Vic Allen" title="Curriculum Director : Creative Digital Media">
    <organisation>UTC Sheffield</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>111 Matilda Street</line>
      <city>Sheffield</city>
      <postcode>S1 4QF</postcode>
    </address>
    <tel>0114 260 3970</tel>
    <email>vallen@utcsheffield.org.uk</email>
  </referee>
  <referee name="Brigidin Crowther" title="Disability Service Manager">
  <organisation>South Yorkshire Disability Service Team</organisation>
  <address>
    <line>3rd Floor Rockingham Court</line>
    <line>152 Rockingham Street</line>
    <city>Sheffield</city>
    <postcode>S1 4EB</postcode>
  </address>
</referee>
<referee name="Brian Quinion" title="Disability Service Manager">
  <organisation>South Yorkshire Disability Service Team</organisation>
  <address>
    <line>3rd Floor Rockingham Court</line>
    <line>152 Rockingham Street</line>
    <city>Sheffield</city>
    <postcode>S1 4EB</postcode>
  </address>
</referee>-->
  <referee name="James Wallbank" title="Proprietor">
    <organisation>Makers</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>555 Abbeydale Road</line>
      <city>Sheffield</city>
      <postcode>S7 1TA</postcode>
    </address>
    <tel>0114 2588431</tel>
    <email>james@makersontheedge.com</email>
  </referee>
  <!--	<referee name="Shirley Hammond" title="Disability Service Manager">
  <organisation>South Yorkshire Disability Service Team</organisation>
  <address>
    <line>3rd Floor Rockingham Court</line>
    <line>152 Rockingham Street</line>
    <city>Sheffield</city>
    <postcode>S1 4EB</postcode>
  </address>
</referee>
<referee name="Dr. Rob Stoneman" title="Director">
  <organisation>Sheffield Wildlife Trust</organisation>
  <address>
    <line>Wood Lane House</line>
    <line>52 Wood Lane</line>
    <line>Hillsborough</line>
    <city>Sheffield</city>
    <postcode>S6 5HE</postcode>
  </address>
</referee>
<referee name="Ms B Broome" title="Director">
  <organisation>Sheffield Churches Council for Community Care</organisation>
  <address>
    <line>Backfields</line>
    <city>Sheffield</city>
    <postcode>S1 4HJ</postcode>
  </address>
  </referee>-->
</cv>
