<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE cv SYSTEM "http://demo1.cmjdevel.co.uk/~martyn/cv/cv.dtd"
[
<!ENTITY nbsp   "&#160;">
<!ENTITY copy   "&#169;">
<!ENTITY pound  "&#163;">
]>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cv.xsl"?>
<cv>
  <candidate>
    <name>Martyn Eggleton</name>
    <address>
      <line>40 Portsea Road</line>
      <line>Hillsborough</line>
      <city>Sheffield</city>
      <postcode>S6 4QB</postcode>
    </address>
    <tel>0114 2214395</tel>
    <mobile>0779 4445457</mobile>
    <email>martyn.eggleton@gmail.com</email>
    <website>stretch.deedah.org</website>
    <dateofbirth>27th July 1976</dateofbirth>
    <nationality>British</nationality>
    <maritalstatus>Married</maritalstatus>
  </candidate>
  <item type="Profile" categories="Programming">A skilled programmer and trainer with over 10 years experience in web
    technologies especially HTML, PHP and JavaScript.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="System Design">Dedicated to bringing the most efficient and
    usable user experience to new and existing systems, by bringing forward innovative ideas and
    developing them into complete systems.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">Good awareness of design, planning &amp; problem solving
    techniques and approaches in a variety of situations from developing functional specifications
    for technical solutions with users, to process development, training, team and capacity building.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="Programming">Experience of high profile and high financial turnover systems
    being the lead developer for the 'Flora London Marathon Exhibition' website and writing for
    systems with an annual turnover in excess of &pound;14 million.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">A hardworking individual with experience of working in small
    teams as well as written, verbal and visual communication.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">An aptitude for software development, systems design and training and coaching.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">A hardworking individual with good interpersonal, written, verbal and visual communications skills and an aptitude for software development, employment advice, training and coaching.</item> 
  <item type="Profile" categories="">Good desktop publishing and web development skills both aesthetically and technically.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">Flexible, adaptable and self developing with an aptitude for picking up ICT systems and techniques (For example I am currently learning JAVA and XUL for two personal projects).</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">Good training and development skills ranging from identifying learners needs to preparing sessions and giving feedback and assessment.</item>
  <item type="Profile" categories="">A keen free and open source software advocate who contributes to and leads various FOSS projects.</item>
  <!--achievements feedback from Joelle-->
  
  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Access-Space</organisation>
    <date>2008-07-01</date>
    <title>Training / Technical Volunteer</title>
    
    <item categories="Linux">Teaching workshops with Access-Space users new to Linux and FOSS on how to choose install and configure a GNU/Linux distribution, using course notes I wrote in preparation (http://knowhow.access-space.org/wiki/doku.php?id=courses:ilit).</item>
    <item categories="Hardware">Teaching some users the parts of a PC and how to select build and test PCs from component parts, also constructing PCs to train on.</item>
    <item categories="Community">Working within a community setting</item>
    <item categories="Hardware">Experience refurbishing second user IT equipment</item>
    <item categories="Training">Running/facilitating workshops, learning environments</item>
    <item categories="Software">Sharing knowledge of Open Source Software utilities and tools (and the ethos behind them) for development with other users including creativity programs, editors and programming libraries.</item>
    <!--<item categories="">Excellent Communication Skills</item>-->
    <item categories="Documentation">A wide range of writing styles from reports through to simple how to documents</item>
    <item categories="">The ability to self manage and prioritise own workload</item>
    <item categories="">Excellent time management</item>

    <item categories="WebDev">Assisting in the creation of various Access-Space Web pages including modifying HTML templates for dokuwiki.</item>
  </experience>
  
  
  
  <experience type="Personal" categories="">
    <item categories="Networking">My entirely Linux based home LAN uses DHCP, Samba file-sharing, firewalls, wireless and other security and admin. Almost all the software on my PCs are covered by OSI approved licences and I encourage people to use things like Firefox and OpenOffice as replacements even on MS Windows machines.</item>
    
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Developed Open Source projects for managing XML OpenSong data using mootools enhanced HTML and PHP, and one for using the Nintendo WiiMote with MIT Scratch children's programming language.</item>
    <item categories="WebDev">Developed own website using dokuwiki and mootools to enhance the HTML.</item>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Designed and implemented early proof of concept for a
      port of OpenSong to XUL using JavaScript and SQLite.</item>
    <item categories="XML">Created customisable CV writing project using XML and XSLT.</item>
  </experience>

  
  
  <experience type="Paid" categories="">
    <organisation>CMJ Management Ltd.</organisation>

    <date>2003-05-01</date>
    <date>2008-06-01</date>

    <title>Software Developer</title>
    <item categories="Hardware">Refurbished old PCs and gambling terminals to build machines for designing T-Shirts for the public at the Flora London Marathon, including building my own thin client Linux distro..</item>
    <item categories="Networking">Configured the refurbished machines into a portable LAN, managing DHCP, firewalls security and admin for thin client machines.</item>
    
    <item categories="">Software Developer on TAMS (Total Agency Management System) which provides
      back office and public websites for booking accommodation and conference facilities and
      equipment and exhibition space.</item>
    <item categories="System Design">Worked closely with internal and external customers
      identifying, proposing and implementing new features to improve user experience.</item>
    <item categories="Databases">Relational Database design and maintenance using PostgreSQL on a
      system comprising of well over 100 tables.</item>
    <item categories="PHP">Developed major 'Hotel Booking Agency Management System' written in
      heavily object oriented PHP. Using an in house framework that I helped to develop, this
      includes extensions to SMARTY.</item>
    <item categories="PHP">Wrote and was responsible for design and maintenance of and user support
      for a user definable report writing module, which can output as HTML, CSV and PDF.</item>
    <item categories="JavaScript">Wrote a cross browser rich Internet application for designing
      lettering for t-shirts and running vests for the Flora London Marathon, in object oriented
      JavaScript using JSON as the communication medium.</item>
    <item categories="JavaScript">Wrote Web 2.0 style JavaScript rendered user interface elements
      for quick searches and situations where there are many small incremental updates to be made.</item>
    <item categories="PHP">Built SVG plotter driver in PHP for HPGL2 based cutter plotters, used for
      taking T-Shirt lettering requests and cutting them out of vinyl.</item>
    <item categories="XML">Wrote graphical exhibition floor-plan designer in SVG and JavaScript.</item>
    <item categories="PHP">Wrote a WYSIWYG user content system that, allowed Exhibitors at the Flora
      London Marathon to add there own content and logos to the lmexpo website safely.</item>
    <item categories="XML">Wrote XML / REST interfaces for connection to partner organisations
      systems, for single sign-in etc. And integration with Google Checkout and WorldPay</item>
    <item categories="PHP">Designed and coded to unit tests for suitable areas of systems, ensuring
      further robustness.</item>
    <!-- robust secure accessible standards compliant -->
  </experience>



  <experience type="Contract" categories="">
    <organisation>jobnet @ burtonstreetproject</organisation>

    <date>2003-05-01</date>
    <date>2003-05-01</date>

    <item categories="Solutions Development">Selected, installed, configured and further developed a
      room booking system, written in PHP and MYSQL.</item>
  </experience>

  <experience type="Paid" categories="">
    <organisation>jobnet @ burtonstreetproject</organisation>

    <date>2002-09-01</date>
    <date>2003-04-01</date>

    <title>Advice Worker / IT Coordinator</title>
    <item categories="Community">Managed the local PCs, laptops, internal and external networking setups for this community based employment advise project.</item>
    <item categories="Advising">Advised and assisted people on job search issues and help them to
      develop and find work.</item>
    <item categories="System Design">Advised on the development of the externally developed Skills
      Register' system to fix it functionality and usability issues.</item>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Developed tools to assist staff in 15 offices to
      classify jobs in to the Standard Occupational Classification Codes, the first version being in
      CHM the second MS Access 2000 and the final one written in PHP.</item>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Developed distributed systems to allow advisers to
      write CVs for clients, track the kind of work they are looking for and do semi automated job
      search on a number of websites.</item>
  </experience>

  <experience type="Paid" categories="">
    <organisation>Jobcentre Plus</organisation>

    <date>2000-06-01</date>
    <date>2002-09-01</date>

    <title>Administration Officer</title>
    <item categories="">Assistant Disability Employment Adviser.</item>
    <item categories="Advising">Assisted disabled jobseekers to find work by advising on employment
      and benefit issues.</item>
    <item categories="">Test Administrator.</item>
    <item categories="">Administered Occupational Psychology Assessment exercises.</item>
    <item categories="">Access to Work Administration Assistant / Assistant Access to Work
      Consultant.</item>
    <item categories="">Assisted the team to administer the programme.</item>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Developed management information and reporting system
      in EXCEL, as a stop gap measure to replace legacy system.</item>
    <item categories="System Design">Was heavily involved from the users side in development of the
      "Functional Specification" for major call centre and work flow management system for the
      'Access To Work' programme DiSC2.</item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid" categories="">
    <organisation>Sheffield Wildlife Trust</organisation>

    <date>1998-11-01</date>
    <date>2001-03-01</date>

    <title>Information and Publicity Manager</title>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Managing all the internal information systems,
      developing 6 database systems, some of which loaded live data into our website using PERL, and
      others that were used for financial tracking, and reserve management.</item>
    <item categories="Design Skills">Responsible for producing SWT's publications including the
      membership magazine Kingfisher and brochures.</item>
    <item categories="System Admin">Administered 10 PC network, installing software, training and
      coaching staff, advising SWT and others on purchasing, and trouble shooting.</item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Paid" categories="">
    <organisation>Crossfield Chemicals</organisation>

    <date>1993-07-01</date>
    <date>1993-09-01</date>

    <title>Thixotropic paint systems researcher</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="School Work Experience" categories="">
    <organisation>Garog</organisation>

    <date>1993-03-01</date>
    <date>1993-03-01</date>

    <title>Digital systems design assistant</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="School Work Experience" categories="">
    <organisation>Heronscan Software Ltd</organisation>

    <date>1992-02-01</date>
    <date>1992-02-01</date>

    <title>Digital control systems design assistant</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Neighbourhood Information Network Enterprise</organisation>

    <date>1998-02-01</date>
    <date>1998-09-01</date>

    <title>Technical Manager</title>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Co-founder and developer for project aiming to use
      information technology to help socially excluded communities help themselves, through
      information, knowledge and resource sharing.</item>
    <item categories="">This involved putting together a draft Neighbourhood Atlas, a 250 page
      website.</item>
  </experience>

  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Netherthorpe and Upperthorpe Community Alliance</organisation>

    <date>1997-10-01</date>
    <date>1998-09-01</date>

    <title>Management Committee Member</title>
    <item categories="">Officer and Executive member for organisation that brings together over 70
      community groups in the area to give local people a say in how regeneration funding is spent.</item>
    <item categories="">Also a member of the committee responsible for the use of European funding,
      and involved in writing the Area Action Plan and the organisation of the community conference
      and consultation on which it was based.</item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>The Word Place</organisation>

    <date>1997-04-01</date>
    <date>1997-12-01</date>

    <title>IT Tutor to ESOL students</title>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Gimme5</organisation>

    <date>1996-05-01</date>
    <date>1996-12-01</date>

    <title>Project team member</title>
  </experience>

  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Students For Sheffield</organisation>

    <date>1996-01-01</date>
    <date>1996-09-01</date>

    <item categories="">Heavily involved in this partnership between students, community and
      business leaders in Sheffield to improve the effectiveness of students in the community.</item>
    <item categories="">I completed the first Leadership in the Community' course in 96, and helped
      stage courses in 97 and 8. Led the Audio and Visual team that staged 3 highly successful
      conferences for 1200 people.</item>
  </experience>
  <experience type="Voluntary" categories="">
    <organisation>Sheffield Electronic Press</organisation>

    <date>1995-09-01</date>
    <date>1996-05-01</date>

    <title>Project Leader</title>
    <item categories=""><!--First e-->Editor &amp; technical manager for the highly successful
      Internet magazine, ShEP.</item>
    <item categories="Solutions Development">Designed and built content management system,
      journalistic / content processes and the layouts for ShEP an early student run Internet
      newspaper.</item>
    <item categories="">Responsible for introducing it's continuing organisational structure and
      initial launch, and setting up and managing many of its technical elements.</item>
    <item categories="">Organised and motivated volunteer reporters, programmers and editorial
      staff.</item>
  </experience>

  <educationitem>
    <organisation>AMT International</organisation>

    <date>1999-08-01</date>
    <date>1999-08-01</date>

    <qualification type="City &amp; Guilds" title="7331 in Training Techniques"/>
  </educationitem>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>University of Sheffield</organisation>

    <date>1994-04-01</date>
    <date>1996-06-01</date>

    <qualification type="BEng" title="Control &amp; Systems Engineering" grade="200 CAT Points"
    />
  </educationitem>
  <educationitem>
    <organisation>Padgate County High School</organisation>

    <date>1987-09-01</date>
    <date>1994-06-01</date>

    <qualification type="A Level" title="Maths" grade="A"/>
    <qualification type="A Level" title="Physics" grade="B"/>
    <qualification type="A Level" title="Economics" grade="C"/>
    <qualification type="A Level" title="General Studies" grade="A"/>

    <qualification type="GCSE" title="Maths" grade="A"/>
    <qualification type="GCSE" title="Dual Award Science" grade="AA"/>
    <qualification type="GCSE" title="English Literature &amp; Language" grade="BB"/>
    <qualification type="GCSE" title="Music" grade="F"/>
    <qualification type="GCSE" title="British Industrial Society" grade="B"/>
    <qualification type="GCSE" title="German" grade="C"/>
  </educationitem>





  <referee categories="Solutions Development" name="John Beeden" title="Exhibition Director">
    <organisation>London Marathon Ltd</organisation>
    <address>
      
      <line>115 Southwark Street</line>
        <line>London</line>
          <line>UK</line>
            <line>SE1 0JF</line>
              
      
    </address>
    <email>john.beeden@lmexpo.com</email>
    <tel>0207 620 4117</tel>
  </referee>
  
  
  

<!-- 
  <referee categories="Solutions Development" name="John Beeden" title="Managing Director">
  <organisation>CMJ Management</organisation>
  <address>
  <line>Bridge Room</line>
  <line>57 Burton Street</line>
  <line>Hillsborough</line>
  <line>Sheffield</line>
  <line>S6 2HH</line>
  </address>
  <email>john.beeden@lmexpo.com</email>
  </referee>
  
  
  
--> 
  
  <referee categories="Solutions Development" name="Joelle Locke" title="Managing Director">
    <organisation>Incorporate Venues</organisation>
    <address>
        <line>7-9 Shaftesbury Street</line>
          <line>Fordingbridge</line>
            <line>Hampshire</line>
              <line>SP6 1JF</line>
    </address>
    <email>joelle.locke@sjjb.co.uk</email>
    <tel>01425 651401</tel>
  </referee>


  <referee categories="Solutions Development" name="Ian Cambe" title="Project Director">
    <organisation>Southey &amp; Owlerton Area Regeneration</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>57 Burton Street</line>
        <line>Hillsborough</line>
          <line>Sheffield</line>
            <line>S6 2HH</line>
    </address>
    <email>icambe@jobnet.burtonstreet.org.uk</email>
    <tel>0114 2496194</tel>
  </referee>

  <!--
  <referee categories="Advising" name="Shirley Hammond" title="Disability Service Manager">
    <organisation>South Yorkshire Disability Service Team</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>3rd Floor Rockingham Court</line>
      <line>152 Rockingham Street</line>
      <line>Sheffield</line>
      <line>S1 4EB</line>
    </address>
  </referee>
  <referee categories="" name="Dr. Rob Stoneman" title="Director">
    <organisation>Sheffield Wildlife Trust</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>Wood Lane House</line>
      <line>52 Wood Lane</line>
      <line>Hillsborough</line>
      <line>Sheffield</line>
      <line>S6 5HE</line>
    </address>
  </referee>
  <referee categories="" name="Ms B Broome" title="Director">
    <organisation>Sheffield Churches Council for Community Care</organisation>
    <address>
      <line>Backfields</line>
      <line>Sheffield</line>
      <line>S1 4HJ</line>
    </address>
  </referee>-->
</cv>
